Mercury Press Records
Mercury Press Records
- Fantasy and Science Fiction (Part II)
  - Editorial records
    - Literary manuscripts
      - Browne, Tom
        - "The Cat Was Black", Mar 1953 (Box 68)
      - Brunner, John
        - "The Vitanuls", Jul 1967 (Box 68)
      - Buck, Doris P.
        - "The Appraiser", Feb 1954 (Box 68)
        - "Aunt Agatha", Oct 1952 (Box 68)
        - "Dywyk", Oct 1955 (Box 68)
        - "Flight Between Realities", Jul 1967 (Box 68)
        - "Two-Bit Oracle", Aug 1954 (Box 68)
      - Budrys, Algis
        - "Cerberus", Dec 1967 (Box 68)
      - Bunch, David R.
        - "That High-Up Blue Day that Saw the Black Sky-Train Come Spinning", Mar 1968 (Box 68)
        - "A Scare in Time", Sep 1968 (Box 68)
        - "Of Time and Us", Jun 1968 (Box 68)
      - Callaghan, Grant C.
        - "The Report", 5 Jun 1956 (Box 68)
      - Caravan, T. P.
        - "Random Sample", Apr 1953 (Box 68)
      - Cardwell, W. D. E.
        - "The Last Man", 24 Apr 1955 (Box 68)
      - Carlson, Esther
        - "Happy Landing", Dec 1952 (Box 68)
        - "Heads You Win...", Apr 1953 (Box 68)
        - "Long Distance", Oct 1953 (Box 68)
        - "Night Life", Dec 1953 (Box 68)
        - "Somewhere East of Rudyard", Feb 1954 (Box 68)
      - Carr, John Dickson
        - "Blind Man's Hood", Jan 1955 (Box 68)
      - Carr, Terry
        - "Sleeping Beauty", May 1967 (Box 68)
      - Carter, Paul A.
        - "Unbalanced Equation", Jan 1956 (Box 68)
      - Cartmill, Cleve
        - "My Lady Smiles", Nov 1953 (Box 68)
        - "Youth, Anybody?", Nov 1955 (Box 68)
      - Cassens, Kenneth H.
        - "The Lonely Worm", Feb 1952 (Box 68)
      - Chandler, Bertram
        - "Jetsam", Apr 1953 (Box 68)
      - Chandler, C. & B.
        - "Simple Psimon", 16 Sep 1954 (Box 68)
      - Chandler, Raymond
        - "The Bronze Door", Oct 1953 (Box 68)
      - Charteris, Leslie
        - "The Darker Drink", Oct 1952 (Box 68)
        - "Fish Story", Jun 1954 (Box 68)
        - "The Man Who Liked Ants", Jun 1953 (Box 68)
      - Christopher, John
        - "The Little People" (Part 1), Jan 1967 (Box 69)
        - "The Little People" (Part 2), Feb 1967 (Box 69)
        - "The Little People" (conclusion), Mar 1967 (Box 69)
      - Clark, Genevieve M.
        - "Planetary Poetry", 14 May 1957 (Box 69)
      - Clark, Johnny
        - Untitled, 2 May 1957 (Box 69)
      - Clarke, Arthur C.
        - "Possible, That's All", Oct 1966 (Box 69)
        - "Security Check", undated (Box 69)
        - "Superiority", Aug 1951 (Box 69)
      - Clarke, Pauline
        - "The Potato Cake", Jun 1955 (Box 69)
      - Cleeve, Brian
        - "The Devil and Jake O'Hara", Aug 1968 (Box 69)
        - "The Devil in Exile", Nov 1968 (Box 69)
      - Clement, Hal
        - "Two Years", undated; 2 folders (Box 69)
      - Clingerman, Mildred
        - "A Day for Waving", 25 Jul 1956 (Box 69)
        - "Minister Without Portfolio", Feb 1952 (Box 69)
        - "Stair Trick", Aug 1952 (Box 69)
        - "Winning Recipe", Nov 1952 (Box 69)
      - Coates, Robert M.
        - "The Return of the Gods", 1950, Winter-Spring (Box 69)
      - Coblentz, Stanton A.
        - "On Another Planet", 2 May 1956 (Box 69)
      - Cockburn, Claud
        - "The Incredulity of Colonel Mumph", Apr 1956 (Box 69)
      - Cogswell, Theodore R.
        - "Threesie", Jan 1956 (Box 69)
      - Coley, Lorraine
        - "Future, Unknown or Known", 26 Nov 1955 (Box 69)
      - Collyn, George
        - "Out of Time, Out of Place", Sep 1967 (Box 69)
      - Coppel, Alfred
        - "The Dreamer", Apr 1952 (Box 69)
        - "Mother", Sep 1952 (Box 69)
      - Correa, Hugo
        - "Alter Ego", Jul 1967 (Box 69)
      - Correy, Lee
        - "The Brass Cannon", Nov 1955 (Box 69)
      - Cotta, Jewel Lucille
        - "Strange Journey", undated (Box 69)
      - Coupling, J. J.
        - "The Good Life", Feb 1952 (Box 69)
      - Cox, Arthur J.
        - "The Twilight Planet", Jun 1951 (Box 69)
      - Cox, Jean
        - "The Sea Change", Mar 1967 (Box 69)
      - Crawford, F. Marion
        - "The Doll's Ghost", Apr 1952 (Box 69)
      - Crody, John T.
        - "Devil Song", 23 Jan 1950 (Box 69)
      - Crossen, Kendell
        - "Whose Move?", 29 Mar 1952 (Box 69)
      - Crow, Leslie
        - "Warrior in Darkness", Jun 1954 (Box 69)
      - Crow, Levi
        - "Young-Man-With-Skull-at-His-Ear", May 1953 (Box 69)
      - Curtis, Betsy
        - "Devine Right", 1950, Summer (Box 69)
        - "A Peculiar People", Aug 1951 (Box 69)
        - "The Science and Art of Dilating the Frammis", 2 Nov 1950 (Box 69)
      - Dance, Clifton
        - "The Brothers", undated (Box 69)
        - "A Matter of Ethics", Nov 1954 (Box 69)
      - Davidson, Avram
        - "My Boy Friend's Name is Jello", Jul 1954 (Box 70)
        - "The Power of Every Root", Oct 1967 (Box 70)
        - "Quick With His Hands", Aug 1967 (Box 70)
      - Davis, Lavinia R.
        - "Randall", Aug 1953 (Box 70)
      - Davis, Steve
        - "Yours Faithful and True", 27 Aug 1957 (Box 70)
      - DeAngelis, Guy
        - "Door to Door", Dec 1953 (Box 70)
      - Deardorf, Kenneth R.
        - "Ganymedeus Sapiens: Modern Scientific Dilemma", Sep 1952 (Box 70)
        - "Skiammetric Morphology and Behaviorism of Ganymedeus Sapiens...", Dec 1951 (Box 70)
      - deCamp, L. Sprague
        - "Dinosaurs in Today's World", Mar 1968 (Box 70)
        - "The Landlocked Indian Ocean", Jun 1969 (Box 70)
        - "Time", Oct 1967 (Box 70)
      - deCamp, L. Sprague & Pratt, Fletcher
        - "The Ancestral Amethyst", Aug 1952 (Box 70)
        - "Beasts of Bourbon", Oct 1951 (Box 70)
        - "The Better Mousetrap", Dec 1950 (Box 70)
        - "The Black Ball", Oct 1952 (Box 70)
        - "Gavagan's Bar", 1950, Winter (Box 70)
        - "The Green Thumb", Feb 1953 (Box 70)
        - "One Man's Meat", Sep 1953 (Box 70)
        - "The Rape of the Lock", Feb 1952 (Box 70)
        - "The Untimely Toper", Jul 1953 (Box 70)
      - Dee, Roger
        - "The Fresh Start", Jan 1954 (Box 70)
        - "Man Friday", Mar 1954 (Box 70)
        - "The Poundstone Paradox", May 1954 (Box 70)
      - DeFoe, Daniel
        - "The Devil at St. Bennet Fynk", Apr 1953 (Box 70)
        - "The Friendly Demon", Feb 1951 (Box 70)
      - deFord, Miriam Allen
        - "The Aljeri Diary", Mar 1968 (Box 70)
        - "The Daughter of the Tree", Aug 1951 (Box 70)
        - "Frustrated Frankenstein: Alfonso Herrera and His Colpoids", Aug 1954 (Box 70)
        - "The Last Generation?", undated (Box 70)
        - "Marty and I", Feb 1956 (Box 70)
        - "The Superior Sex", undated (Box 70)
      - DeLany, Samuel R.
        - "Corona", Oct 1967 (Box 70)
        - "Films" BARBARELLA, Feb 1969 (Box 70)
        - "Films" CHARLY, Jan 1969 (Box 70)
        - "Films" 2001: A SPACE ODYSSEY, Aug 1968 (Box 70)
        - "Lines of Power", May 1968 (Box 70)
      - Deming, Richard
        - "The Shape of Things that Came", Oct 1951 (Box 70)
      - de Moncrif, François-Auguste Paradis
        - "The Cat, the Brahmin and the Penitent", Dec 1954 (Box 70)
      - Dennis, Adam
        - "You Must Love Somebody", undated (Box 70)
      - Derleth, August
        - "Who Shall I Say is Calling?", Aug 1952 (Box 70)
      - Dewey, G. Gordon
        - "The Tooth", Aug 1952 (Box 70)
      - Dick, Philip K.
        - "Expendable", Jul 1953 (Box 70)
        - "The Father Thing", Dec 1954 (Box 70)
        - "Roog", Feb 1953 (Box 70)
      - Dickinson, Patric
        - "The Ape at the Typewriter", Aug 1955 (Box 70)
      - Dickson, Gordon R.
        - "Listen", Aug 1952 (Box 70)
        - "Miss Prinks", Jun 1954 (Box 70)
        - "Of the People", Dec 1955 (Box 70)
        - "Our First Death", Aug 1955 (Box 70)
      - Disch, Thomas M.
        - "Moondust, the Smell of Hay, and Dialectical Materialism", Aug 1967 (Box 70)
        - "Problems of Creativeness", Apr 1967 (Box 70)
      - Dorman, Sonya
        - "Lunatic Assignment", Jan 1968 (Box 71)
      - Drake, Leah Bodine
        - "The Gods of the Dana", Jul 1954 (Box 71)
        - "The Jannigogs", Apr 1954 (Box 71)
        - "The Woods Grow Darker", Nov 1955 (Box 71)
        - "The Word of Willow", Sep 1956 (Box 71)
      - Drussai, Garen
        - "Extra-Curricular", Aug 1952 (Box 71)
      - Dunsany, Lord
        - "Told Under Oath", Aug 1953 (Box 71)
      - Edmondson, G. C.
        - "Technological Retreat", May 1956 (Box 71)
      - Eisenberg, Larry
        - "The Saga of Dmm", Dec 1967 (Box 71)
        - "The Time of His Life", Apr 1968 (Box 71)
        - "The Two Lives of Ben Coulter", Apr 1967 (Box 71)
      - Elgin, Suzette Haden
        - "For the Sake of Grace", May 1969 (Box 71)
      - Elliot, Bruce
        - "The Devil Was Sick", Apr? 1951 (Box 71)
        - "Fearsome Fable", Feb 1951 (Box 71)
        - "The Last Magician", Jan 1953 (Box 71)
        - "Wolves Don't Cry", Apr 1954 (Box 71)
      - Ellis, H. F.
        - "Space-Crime Continuum", Sep 1954 (Box 71)
      - Ellison, Harlan
        - "Santa Claus Vs. S.P.I.D.E.R.", Jan 1969 (Box 71)
        - "Try a Dull Knife", Oct 1968 (Box 71)
      - Endore, Guy
        - "Men of Iron", undated (Box 71)
      - Etchison, Dennis
        - "A Walk in the Wet", Feb 1967 (Box 71)
      - Farmer, Philip Jose
        - "Attitudes", Oct 1953 (Box 71)
      - Felsen, Henry Gregor
        - "The Spaceman Cometh", Apr 1956 (Box 71)
      - Filer, Burt
        - "Backtracked", Jun 1968 (Box 71)
      - Finney, Jack
        - "Quit Zoomin' Those Hands Through the Air", Dec 1952 (Box 71)
        - "There is a Tide", Jul 1954 (Box 71)
        - "The Third Level", Oct 1952 (Box 71)
      - Fish, Robert L.
        - "To Hell With the Odds", Feb 1968 (Box 71)
      - Fitzpatrick, R. C.
        - "Dead to Rights", Apr 1968 (Box 71)
      - Frazer, Shamus
        - "The Cyclops Juju", Sep 1967 (Box 71)
      - Friborg, Albert Compton
        - "Careless Love", Jul 1954 (Box 71)
      - Friedman, Bruce Jay
        - "The Investor", Mar 1967 (Box 71)
      - Fyfe, H. B.
        - "Ransom", Feb 1952 (Box 71)
        - "The Well-Oiled Machine", Dec 1950 (Box 71)
      - Gage, Joseph H.
        - "Achilles Had His Heel", Oct 1951 (Box 71)
      - Galouye, Daniel F.
        - "The Flight of Fancy", Apr 1968 (Box 71)
        - "The Pliable", 9 Nov 1955 (Box 71)
        - "Sanctuary", Feb 1954 (Box 71)
      - Gardner, Martin
        - "No-Sided Professor", Feb 1951 (Box 71)
        - "The Slapenarski Triangle", undated (Box 71)
      - Garrett, Randall
        - "Infinite Resources", Jul 1954 (Box 71)
        - "The Purist's Complaint", 3 Sep 1953 (Box 71)
      - Gault, William Campbell
        - "Joy Ride", Jan 1953 (Box 71)
      - Gilbert, Doris
        - "Arrangement in Green", Feb 1954 (Box 71)
        - "The Chocolate Coach", Jan 1953 (Box 71)
      - Goggin, Richard
        - "Francis Harkins", Dec 1952 (Box 71)
      - Goldman, Lawrence
        - "Temporarily at Liberty", Feb 1951 (Box 71)
      - Goldsmith, Ruth M.
        - "Yankee Exodus", Jul 1953 (Box 71)
      - Goldstone, Herbert
        - "Virtuoso", Feb 1953 (Box 71)
      - Goligorsky, Eduardo
        - "When the Birds Die", 1967 (Box 71)
      - Gotlieb, Phyllis
        - "Planetoid Idiot", May 1967 (Box 71)
      - Goulart, Ron
        - "Conroy's Public", Dec 1952 (Box 72)
        - "Cop State", May 1969 (Box 72)
        - "Fill in the Blank", May 1967 (Box 72)
        - "Gadget Man", Dec 1968 (Box 72)
        - "The Ghost Patrol", Oct 1968 (Box 72)
        - "Letters to the Editor", Apr 1952 (Box 72)
        - "Muscadine", Apr 1968 (Box 72)
        - "The Sword Swallower", Nov 1967 (Box 72)
      - Grant, C. L.
        - "The House of Evil", Dec 1968 (Box 72)
      - Graves, Robert
        - "An Appointment for Candlemas", Oct 1955 (Box 72)
        - "The Shout", Apr 1952 (Box 72)
      - Green, Joseph
        - "An Affair With Genius", Mar 1969 (Box 72)
      - Green, Robert M., Jr.
        - "The Royal Road to There", Jun 1967 (Box 72)
      - Greene, Graham
        - "Proof Positive", undated (Box 72)
      - Gresham, William Lindsay
        - "The Dream Dust Factory", Dec 1953 (Box 72)
        - "The Star Gypsies", Jul 1953 (Box 72)
      - Griffith, Ann Warren
        - "Captive Audience", Aug 1953 (Box 72)
      - Grimes, Lee
        - "Lease on Life", Nov 1954 (Box 72)
      - Grinnell, David
        - "Malice Aforethought", Nov 1952 (Box 72)
        - "The Rag Thing", Oct 1951 (Box 72)
      - Gross, Marion
        - "The Good Provider", Sep 1952 (Box 72)
      - Grow, Julian F.
        - "The Sword of Pell the Idiot", Apr 1967 (Box 72)
      - Gruber, Frank
        - "Piece of Eight", Nov 1955 (Box 72)
        - "The Thirteenth Floor" (Box 72)
      - Hale, Edward Everett
        - "Hands Off", Feb 1952 (Box 72)
      - Hamm, Thelma
        - "Gallie's House", Sep 1953 (Box 72)
      - Harness, Charles
        - "Bugs", Aug 1967 (Box 72)
        - "The Chess Players", Oct 1953 (Box 72)
        - "Child by Chronos", Jun 1953 (Box 72)
        - "The Prisoner", Dec 1952 (Box 72)
      - Harris, Joseph
        - "A Scare for Timothy", Nov 1968 (Box 72)
      - Harrison, Harry
        - "I Have My Vigil", Feb 1968 (Box 72)
        - "The Secret of Stonehenge", Jun 1968 (Box 72)
      - Harrison, M. John
        - "London Melancholy", May 1969 (Box 72)
      - Harrison, Michael
        - "Pull Devil, Pull Baker", Jun 1969 (Box 72)
        - "Some Very Odd Happenings at Kibblesham Manor House", Apr 1969 (Box 72)
      - Hart, James S.
        - "The House in Arbor Lane", Dec 1951 (Box 72)
        - "The Traitor", 1953, Fall (Box 72)
      - Heard, Gerald
        - "The Marble Ear", Dec 1952 (Box 72)
      - Heard, H. F.
        - "The Collector", Aug 1951 (Box 72)
      - Heinlein, Robert
        - "Jeff and the Menace from Earth", undated (Box 72)
        - "Star Lummox", May 1954 (Box 72)
      - Henderson, Zenna
        - "The Anything Box", undated (Box 73)
        - "Ararat", Oct 1952 (Box 73)
        - "Come on, Wagons", Dec 1951 (Box 73)
        - "Food to A11 Flesh", Dec 1953 (Box 73)
        - "The Indelible Kind", Dec 1968 (Box 73)
        - "Loo Ree", Feb 1953 (Box 73)
        - "Pottage", 6 May 1955 (Box 73)
      - Hensley, Joe L.
        - "Argent Blood", Aug 1967 (Box 73)
      - Hershman, Morris
        - "The Happy Traitor", Jun 1953 (Box 73)
      - Herzog, Tom
        - "Investigating the Curiosity Drive", Nov 1968 (Box 73)
      - Hickey, H. B.
        - "Hilda", undated (Box 73)
      - Holding, Elisabeth Sanxay
        - "Friday the Nineteenth", 1950, Summer (Box 73)
        - "Shadow of Wings", Jul 1954 (Box 73)
        - "The Strange Children", Aug 1955 (Box 73)
      - Hornsby, E. C.
        - "Overlooked", Mar 1955 (Box 73)
      - Howard, Hayden
        - "Beyond Words", Jul 1968 (Box 73)
      - Howard, Robert E & deCamp, L. Sprague
        - "The Hall of the Dead", Feb 1967 (Box 73)
      - Hoyle, Fred
        - "Blackmail", Feb 1967 (Box 73)
        - "Zoomen", Mar 1967 (Box 73)
      - Hubbard, P. M.
        - "Botany Bay", Feb 1955 (Box 73)
        - "The House", Apr 1969 (Box 73)
        - "Manuscript Found in a Vacuum", Aug 1953 (Box 73)
      - Humphries, Emyr
        - "The Girl in the Ice", Jan 1955 (Box 73)
      - Hunter, Gene
        - "Journey", Feb 1951 (Box 73)
      - Iams, Jack
        - "The Hat in the Hall", 1950, Summer (Box 73)
      - Jackson, Shirley
        - "Bulletin", Mar 1954 (Box 73)
        - "One Ordinary Day, With Peanuts", Jan 1955 (Box 73)
      - Jacobs, Harvey
        - "The Egg of the Glak", Mar 1968 (Box 73)
      - Jaffray, Norman R.
        - "Cowboy Lament", Jan 1954 (Box 73)
        - "Death in the Fission Chamber", circa Mar 1947 (Box 73)
        - "The Thinker Needs a Wife", Apr 1954 (Box 73)
      - Jakes, John W.
        - "Machine", Apr 1952 (Box 73)
      - James, Henry
        - "The Friends of the Friends", Jul 1953 (Box 73)
      - Jenkins, Powell, Jr.
        - "The Mouse With the Twisted Foot", Jan 1954 (Box 73)
      - Jennings, Dave
        - "The Gingerbread Man", May 1954 (Box 73)
      - Jennings, Gary
        - "After All the Dreaming Ends", Feb 1969 (Box 73)
      - Jesby, Ed
        - "Ogre", Sep 1968 (Box 73)
      - Jonas, Gerald
        - "The First Postulate", Jun 1967 (Box 73)
      - Jones, D. F.
        - "Black Snowstorm", Jan 1969 (Box 73)
        - "Coffee Break", Oct 1968 (Box 73)
      - Jordan, Henry
        - "The Cardsharp", undated (Box 73)
      - Kelly, Dan
        - "Perchance to Dream", 20 Oct 1949 (Box 73)
      - Kelly, Dan & Cartmill, Cleve
        - "Nor Iron Bars", Aug 1952 (Box 73)
      - Kelly, Leo P.
        - "Coins", Nov 1968 (Box 73)
      - Kemp, Lysander
        - "The Airborne Baserunner", May 1954 (Box 73)
      - Kendall, Stuart
        - "Posthumous Award", undated (Box 73)
      - Kerr, Walter H.
        - "From a Terran Travel Folder", Feb 1968 (Box 73)
      - King, C. Daly
        - "Dianetics: The Modern Science of Mental Health", Dec 1950; book review (Box 73)
      - Kirk, Russell
        - "Balgrummo's Hell", Jul 1967 (Box 73)
        - "What Shadows We Pursue", Jan 1953 (Box 73)
      - Knarr, Emilie
        - "Carne Vale", Feb 1953 (Box 74)
      - Kneale, Nigel
        - "Peg", Oct 1954 (Box 74)
      - Knight, Damon
        - About "Dick Jones", 21 May 1955 (Box 74)
        - "Not With a Bang", 1950, Winter (Box 74)
      - Koontz, Dean R.
        - "To Behold the Sun", Dec 1967 (Box 74)
        - "The Psychedelic Children", Jul 1968 (Box 74)
        - "Soft Come the Dragons", Aug 1967 (Box 74)
        - "The Twelfth Bed", Aug 1968 (Box 74)
      - Kornbluth, C. M.
        - "The Goodly Creatures", Dec 1952 (Box 74)
        - "I Never Ast No Favors", Apr 1954 (Box 74)
      - Kreigh, Ben
        - "Dianetics: The Modern Science of Mental Health", undated; book review (Box 74)
      - LaFarge, Oliver
        - "John the Revelator", Feb 1951 (Box 74)
        - "The Time Watcher", Feb 1953 (Box 74)
      - Lafferty, R. A.
        - "Camels and Dromedaries, Clem", Oct 1967 (Box 74)
      - Landon, Perceval
        - "Thurnley Abbey", 1949, Fall (Box 74)
      - Lang, Allen
        - "Epitaph For an Iron Man, undated (Box 74)
      - Langdon, John
        - "The Man Who Could Smell Land", Aug 1951 (Box 74)
      - Lanier, Sterling E.
        - "The Kings of the Sea", Nov 1968 (Box 74)
        - "The Leftovers", Mar 1969 (Box 74)
        - "Soldier Key", Aug 1968 (Box 74)
        - "Whose Short Happy Life?", Mar 1968 (Box 74)
      - Lasswitz, Kurd
        - "Aladdin's Lamp", May 1953 (Box 74)
      - Latham, Philip
        - "After Enfer", Mar 1969 (Box 74)
      - Laumer, Keith
        - "The Day Before Forever" (p 1-110), Jul 1967 (Box 74)
        - "The Day Before Forever" (p 111-222), Jul 1967 (Box 74)
        - "Once There Was a Giant", Nov 1968 (Box 74)
      - Lawton, Harry
        - "Extracts From a Bibliomaniac's Journal", Sep 1952 (Box 74)
      - Lee, Edward
        - "Kalato", Dec 1954 (Box 74)
      - Lee, William M.
        - "A Message From Charity", Nov 1967 (Box 74)
        - "Sea Home", Jun 1968 (Box 74)
        - "Trouble on Kort", Apr 1969 (Box 74)
      - Leiber, Fritz
        - "The Big Holiday", Jan 1953 (Box 74)
        - "The Inner Circles", Oct 1967 (Box 74)
        - "The Turned Off Heads", Jan 1968 (Box 74)
        - "When the Last Gods Die", Dec 1951 (Box 74)
      - Leimert, John
        - "John Thomas's Cube", Aug 1951 (Box 74)
      - Leman, Bob
        - "Bait", Jan 1967 (Box 74)
      - Lewis, C. S.
        - "The Shoddy-Lands", Feb 1956 (Box 74)
      - Liddell, C. H.
        - "Android", Jun 1951 (Box 75)
      - Lindner, Robert
        - "The Jet-Propelled Couch", Jan 1956 (Box 75)
      - Linklater, Eric
        - "Sealskin Trousers", Apr 1952 (Box 75)
      - London, Jack
        - "A Thousand Deaths", Sep 1967 (Box 75)
      - Lord, Mindret
        - "Dr. Jacobus Melliflore's Last Patient", Nov 1953 (Box 75)
      - Lory, Robert
        - "The Locator", Feb 1968 (Box 75)
      - Lowe, Roger
        - "Who Counts?", undated (Box 75)
      - Lucas, Jon
        - "Repeat Business", Jun 1969 (Box 75)
      - Ludwig, Edward W.
        - "Occupation", May 1953 (Box 75)
      - Lynch, Harold, Jr.
        - "Artists at Work", undated (Box 75)
      - Lyon, Dana
        - "Mr. Elsie Smith", May 1953 (Box 75)
      - MacAhren, Fay
        - "Bomb 20394856-7", 18 Nov 1954 (Box 75)
      - McAllister, Bruce
        - "Benji's Pencil", Mar 1969 (Box 75)
        - "Prime-Time Teaser", Dec 1968 (Box 75)
        - "Without a Doubt Dream", Apr 1968 (Box 75)
      - McCaffrey, Anne
        - "A Meeting of Minds", Jan 1969 (Box 75)
      - McClintic, Winona
        - "The Anti Climax", Jan 1956 (Box 75)
        - "The Antiquary", Jul 1953 (Box 75)
        - "His Master's Voice", Jun 1953 (Box 75)
        - "In the Days of Our Fathers", 1949, Fall (Box 75)
        - "There Did Not Remain a Word to Say", May 1953 (Box 75)
        - "The Two Voices", Jun 1953 (Box 75)
        - "The Unquiet Grave", Aug 1953 (Box 75)
        - "The Vampire", Jul 1953 (Box 75)
      - McComas, J. Francis
        - "Brave New World", Sep 1954 (Box 75)
      - McCormack, Ford
        - "?", Jun 1951 (Box 75)
      - MacDonald, John D.
        - "Labor Supply", May 1953 (Box 75)
      - MacDonald, Philip
        - "Private - Keep Out!", 1949, Fall (Box 75)
        - "Res Ex Machina", 27 Mar 1954 (Box 75)
        - "Solitary Confinement", Aug 1951 (Box 75)
      - M'ntosh (McIntosh), J.T.
        - "Beggars All", Apr 1953 (Box 75)
        - "One in Three Hundred", 1 Feb 1953 (Box 75)
        - "One Too Many", Sep 1954 (Box 75)
        - "The Saw and the Carpenter", Sep 1967 (Box 75)
        - "Selection", Jan 1955 (Box 75)
        - "Talents", Oct 1952 (Box 75)
      - McKenna, Richard
        - "Home the Hard Way", Oct 1967 (Box 75)
        - "They Are Not Robbed", Jan 1968 (Box 75)
      - McKnight, John P.
        - "Bird Talk", Apr 1953 (Box 75)
        - "Prolog", Aug 1951 (Box 75)
      - MacLeod, Ann
        - "Settle", Jun 1968 (Box 75)
      - McMorron, Tom, Jr.
        - "Leap Year Day", May 1953 (Box 75)
      - Madden, David
        - "The Master's Thesis", Jul 1967 (Box 76)
      - Maddux, Rachel
        - "Final Clearance", Feb 1956 (Box 76)
      - Malko, George
        - "The Flower Kid Cashes In", May 1969 (Box 76)
      - Mallette, Mose
        - "The Stars Know", Feb 1968 (Box 76)
      - Manhattan, Avro
        - "The Cricket Ball", Oct 1955 (Box 76)
      - Marks, Winston
        - "Call Me Adam", Feb 1954 (Box 76)
      - Marsh, Willard
        - "Machina Ex Machina", May 1956 (Box 76)
      - Matheson, Richard
        - "Born of Man and Woman", 1950, Summer (Box 76)
        - "Dress of White Silk", Oct 1951 (Box 76)
        - "The Test", Nov 1954 (Box 76)
      - Maurois, Andre
        - "The War Against the Moon", 1950, Summer (Box 76)
      - Meadows, Patrick
        - "Pater One Pater Two", Feb 1969 (Box 76)
        - "Virtue 'Tis a Fugue!", Apr 1967 (Box 76)
      - Merril, Judith
        - "Books", 1967, Jan - Apr 1969; 6 folders (Box 76)
        - "Project Nursemaid", Oct 1955; 2 folders (Box 76)
        - "Rescue Party", undated (Box 76)
        - "The (Very) Private Life of Edna Appleby", circa Jun 1956 (Box 76)
      - Merwin, Sam, Jr.
        - "Lambikin", undated (Box 76)
      - Middleton, Richard
        - "Shepherd's Boy", Mar 1953 (Box 76)
      - Miller, Lion
        - "The Available Data on the Worp Reaction", Sep 1953 (Box 76)
        - "The Strange History of Worp's Principle", 15 Oct 1952 (Box 76)
      - Miller, P. Schuyler
        - "Daydream", Jan 1956 (Box 76)
      - Moore, E. A.
        - "The Next Step", Feb 1967 (Box 76)
      - Moore, Ward
        - "Bring the Jubilee", Nov 1952 (Box 77)
        - "Lot", May 1953 (Box 77)